[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
* *
**
[bubbling]
[冒泡]
[customers snoring, groaning]
[顾客打鼾、呻吟]
- Just go!
- Oh, no.
- 走吧！
- 哦，不。
- Yes, I will have
a quad patty,
- 是的，我会有
四块肉饼，
with a sprinkling
of Himalayan salt,
洒
喜马拉雅盐，
smoked paprika,
and micro greens.
烟熏辣椒粉，
和微型果岭。
- Gimme a quad--
- Hold on.
- 给我一个四边形 -
- 等一下。
I'm not finished with my order.
我的订单还没完成。
customers: Aw, come on!
顾客：噢，来吧！
- I would like my patties
be-cheesed,
- 我想要我的肉饼
干酪，
but not just any cheese will do.
但并非任何奶酪都可以。
Have you any aged "how-uda"?
你有老年“how-uda”吗？
[customers grumbling]
And yes,
[顾客抱怨]
是的，
it is pronounced "how-uda,"
它的发音是“how-uda”
not "goo-da."
- [growling]
不是“好达”。
- [咆哮]
Just eat the regular
Krabby Patty
吃普通的就可以了
蟹肉饼
and stop wasting
everybody's time!
并停止浪费
每个人的时间！
- Mr. Krabs!
- 蟹老板！
You know we don't
treat our customers like that.
你知道我们不
像这样对待我们的客户。
[ascending xylophone notes]
[上升木琴音符]
It says right here,
in the Krusty Krab manual.
就在这里说，
在蟹堡王手册中。
[clears throat]
"The customer is always right,
[清嗓子]
“顾客永远是对的，
when they have money."
- Oh!
当他们有钱的时候。”
- 哦！
Such wise and beautiful words.
如此智慧而美丽的话语。
Thanks for reminding me,
SpongeBob.
谢谢你提醒我，
海绵宝宝。
- I'm here to serve,
Mr. Krabs.
- 我来这里是为了服务，
蟹老板。
[soars, splats]
[飞翔，啪啪]
- [growsl, screams]
Ketchup waster!
- [咆哮，尖叫]
浪费番茄酱！
- [whimpers]
- [呜咽]
- Oh!
Sorry, SpongeBob.
- 哦！
对不起，海绵宝宝。
I didn't mean it.
No more outbursts.
我不是故意的。
不再爆发。
I'll be nice Mr. Krabs,
I promise.
我会很好的蟹蟹先生
我保证。
- Your napkin.
- [grunts]
- 你的餐巾。
- [咕哝]
- [growling]
- [咆哮]
Waster!
浪费！
[panicked music]
[惊慌的音乐]
[shouting incoherently]
[语无伦次地喊叫]
- [shouts, pants]
- Hmm?
- [喊叫，裤子]
- 嗯？
Ow!
Mr. Krabs!
噢！
蟹老板！
You gotta calm down!
- [shouting incoherently]
你必须冷静！
- [语无伦次地喊叫]
[all screaming]
[所有人尖叫]
- [struggling]
- [挣扎]
* *
**
- Oh!
- [shouting]
- 哦！
- [喊叫]
[yelps]
[尖叫声]
[shouting]
- [growls]
[喊叫]
- [咆哮]
I'll murder-lize him!
我要杀了他！
- Relax, little crab guy.
- 放松点，小螃蟹家伙。
- [growling]
Get your muscled mitts off me!
- [咆哮]
把你肌肉发达的手套从我身上拿开！
Get off!
下车！
Get...
[sighs happily]
得到...
[高兴地叹气]
That's right.
Give in to the healing power
这是正确的。
屈服于治愈的力量
of my pecs.
- I feel so secure.
我的胸肌。
- 我感觉很安全。
- [sighs]
All better?
- [叹气]
一切都好些了吗？
- What?
You let him go?
- 什么？
你让他走了？
We're all dead!
[shouting]
我们都死了！
[喊叫]
[shouts, struggles]
[喊叫、挣扎]
[sizzling]
Ow!
[嘶嘶声]
噢！
The grill's still on!
烤架还开着！
[shouting]
[喊叫]
[wailing]
[哀号]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- I don't know
what's wrong with me.
- 我不知道
我怎么了。
The Krusty Krab's
just been so busy.
蟹堡王店
只是太忙了。
I never seem to get a break.
我似乎从来没有休息过。
- Sounds like someone
needs a vacation.
- 听起来像某人
需要休假。
- I--I could use
some me time.
- 我--我可以使用
一些我的时间。
- And don't worry.
Squidward and I can take care
- 别担心。
章鱼哥和我可以照顾
of the Krusty Krab
while you're gone.
蟹堡王的
当你离开的时候。
- Hmm...
- 唔...
[terrifying string music]
[恐怖的弦乐]
- Order up!
- 订购吧！
- [screams]
I'm sorry,
- [尖叫]
对不起，
but I can't leave
you guys in charge.
但我不能离开
你们负责。
I need a strong man
to run this place--
我需要一个坚强的男人
经营这个地方——
someone who's a rock
坚如磐石的人
and can really handle the load,
you know?
并且能够真正承受负载，
你知道吗？
But who has
that kind of strength, hmm?
但谁有
那种力量，嗯？
- Psst, psst!
[stammers excitedly]
- 嘘，嘘！
[兴奋地结巴]
- That's it!
Larry,
- 就是这样！
拉里，
how would you like
to manage the Krusty Krab
你想要怎样
管理蟹堡王
while I'm on vacation?
当我在度假的时候？
- Larry's got
his own gym to run.
- 拉里有
他自己的健身房去经营。
- Come on, Larry.
It'll be fun.
- 来吧，拉里。
会很有趣的。
- Larry loves fun!
I'm in.
- 拉里喜欢玩乐！
我进来了
- All right!
- 好的！
Ah!
- [groans]
啊!
- [呻吟]
- [groans]
[bubbling]
[冒泡]
- Oh, hey, Larry.
How you liking your new job?
- 哦，嘿，拉里。
你喜欢你的新工作吗？
- Larry likes it just fine.
- 拉里很喜欢。
But do the customers
always eat like this?
但顾客们是否
总是这样吃吗？
[all chomping obnoxiously]
[都令人讨厌地咀嚼着]
- Oh, no.
They normally eat like this!
- 哦，不。
平时他们都是这样吃的！
[grunting, chomping]
[咕噜声，咀嚼声]
- Those poor people.
- 那些可怜的人。
Someone needs to whip them
into shape.
需要有人鞭打他们
成形。
[meat squelching]
【绞肉】
[bubbling]
[冒泡]
- What'll you have?
- Uh...
- 你要什么？
- 呃...
I'll have a double Krabby Patty,
Krabby fries,
我要一份双层蟹肉饼
蟹黄薯条，
and, uh--whoa!
而且，呃——哇！
- [grunts]
- What else?
- [咕哝]
- 还有什么？
- Uh, uh--
a Krabby soda...
- 呃，呃--
蟹黄苏打水...
Uh, uh--
a Krabby...
呃，呃——
一个蟹蟹...
[debris clatters]
My leg!
[碎片碰撞声]
我的腿！
- [laughs]
Hey!
- [笑]
嘿！
[voice warbling]
Can I help you?
[声音颤抖]
我可以帮你吗？
- Yeah, I'll take
a Krabby salad,
- 是的，我会接受
蟹黄沙拉，
dressing on the side,
and 60 more minutes
一边穿衣服，
还有 60 分钟
on this rad treadmill.
在这个拉德跑步机上。
- [warbling]
Here's your change.
- [颤音]
这是你的零钱。
[bubbling]
[冒泡]
- Here's your order, sir.
- 这是您的命令，先生。
- [struggles]
- And don't forget
- [挣扎]
- 别忘了
your side salad!
你的配菜沙拉！
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
- Yeah!
Push it, push it!
- 是的！
推啊推啊！
- Push it, push it!
- 推它，推它！
- [grunts]
Okay, okay.
- [咕哝]
好吧，好吧。
I'll push it.
[grunting]
我来推一下
[咕噜声]
- Push it, push it!
- Yeah, push it!
- 推它，推它！
- 是的，推它！
- [grunting, sighs]
- [咕哝，叹气]
- Yes!
You made it!
- 是的！
你成功了！
Now, claim
your Krabby Patty!
现在，索赔
你的蟹肉饼！
- [weakly]
Hooray...
- [微弱]
万岁...
[snores]
- Aww, too pooped
[打鼾]
- 哇哦，太拉屎了
for a Krabby Patty.
蟹肉饼。
- Ah, forget Krabby Patties.
- 啊，忘了蟹肉饼吧。
Those things are over.
- But Larry,
那些事情都结束了。
- 但是拉里，
Krabby Patties are why
people come here.
蟹肉饼是为什么
人们来到这里。
- Ooh, not anymore.
Now we only serve salads
- 哦，不再是了。
现在我们只提供沙拉
and protein power shakes!
和蛋白质能量奶昔！
- Ooh, power shake!
I wanna taste.
- 哦，权力震动！
我想尝尝。
[slurps]
[啜饮]
[grunts, spits]
[咕哝声，吐口水]
[pants]
[裤子]
- You like?
- No, Larry.
- 你喜欢吗？
- 不，拉里。
No.
- But it gets you jacked!
不。
- 但这会让你被骗！
- I don't wanna be jacked.
- 我不想被骗。
I just want
my Krabby Patties back.
我只想
我的蟹黄饼回来了。
- Everybody wants to get jacked.
- Yeah, jacked!
- 每个人都想被骗。
- 是啊，被骗了！
[both grunting forcefully]
[两人都用力咕哝]
* *
**
- Look, Larry,
I really think
- 看，拉里，
我真的认为
we should go back
to serving Krabby Patties.
我们应该回去
供应蟹黄肉饼。
People love the...
- [exhales]
人们喜欢...
- [呼气]
- Larry?
- [stammers] Jacked.
- 拉里？
- [结巴] 被劫持了。
[bubbling]
[冒泡]
[customers whimpering]
[顾客呜咽]
- SpongeBob!
- 海绵宝宝！
Squidward!
Let's move it, boys.
章鱼哥！
让我们移动它吧，孩子们。
Get those power shakes out
and those heart rates up!
消除那些权力动摇
心率上升！
[both panting fearfully]
[两人都惊恐地喘着气]
- [babbling weakly]
- [微弱地胡言乱语]
[grunts, shouts]
- Sorry!
[咕哝声，喊叫声]
- 对不起！
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
[shouts]
- [laughing]
[喊叫]
- [笑]
- Whoa!
- [struggling]
- 哇！
- [挣扎]
- [slurps, sighs]
- Oh!
- [啜饮，叹气]
- 哦！
- Horrible sustenance.
- 可怕的食物。
- [whimpering]
- [呜咽]
- [shouts, grunts]
- [喊叫声，咕哝声]
[groaning, grunting]
[呻吟，咕哝]
- Let's get outta here!
- 我们离开这里吧！
- Pardon my reach.
-请原谅我的触及范围。
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
[both struggling]
Go on without me!
[双方都在挣扎]
没有我就继续吧！
- [whimpers, shouts]
- No, wait, don't.
- [呜咽，喊叫]
- 不，等等，不要。
- Squidward,
I know Larry means well,
- 章鱼哥，
我知道拉里的本意是好的
but he's messing up
the Krusty Krab!
但他搞砸了
蟹堡王！
This used to be a shrine
to the delicious Krabby Patty.
这里曾经是一座神社
美味的蟹肉饼。
Now it's just a stinky gym.
现在只是一个臭气熏天的健身房。
- Feel...the...burn!
- 感受……燃烧！
[rock music]
[摇滚乐]
- [struggling]
- [挣扎]
[shouts]
[喊叫]
* *
**
- Squidward,
go tell Larry he's fired.
- 章鱼哥，
去告诉拉里他被解雇了。
- Are you crazy?
He is way too big for that.
- 你疯了？
他太大了，做不到这一点。
We need to come at this
another way--
我们需要解决这个问题
另一种方式——
a smart, dignified way!
聪明、有尊严的方式！
I know--
We'll sabotage the place.
我知道——
我们会破坏这个地方。
- [slurping]
- [发出声音]
- And I know
just where to start:
- 我知道
从哪里开始：
the power shakes.
- I'm on it!
力量震动。
- 我来了！
[giggles]
- Wait, wait--what about me?
[咯咯笑]
- 等等，等等——那我呢？
- [singing]
- [唱歌]
Butter!
Lard!
黄油！
猪油！
Mayonnaise.
[grunts happily]
蛋黄酱。
[高兴地咕哝]
[beachy music]
[海滩音乐]
[blender whirring]
[搅拌机嗡嗡作响]
And now, fry it all up
into a greasy,
现在，把它全部炒起来
变成油腻的，
heart-stopping surprise!
令人心碎的惊喜！
Here you go.
干得好。
* *
**
- I'm loving
this oily concoction.
- 我很爱
这种油腻的混合物。
It really makes
Larry's muscles pop!
确实让
拉里的肌肉爆了！
[grunting forcefully]
[用力咕哝]
- [stifles shout]
- Thanks, SpongeBob.
- [窒息喊叫]
- 谢谢，海绵宝宝。
- [groaning]
- [呻吟]
Okay, that failed.
What now?
好吧，失败了。
现在怎么办？
- We'll sabotage
the weight machines.
- 我们会破坏
举重机。
Then these muscle heads will
have to find a new place
然后这些肌肉头就会
必须找到一个新地方
to work out!
- Gotcha.
锻炼身体！
- 明白了。
- Wait, you idiot!
Get me out of here.
- 等等，你这个白痴！
带我离开这里。
* *
**
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[shouts]
[喊叫]
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
[shouting]
[喊叫]
[growls, shouts]
[咆哮，喊叫]
Awesome workout, bro!
锻炼得真棒，兄弟！
[defeated music]
[败乐]
- Oh, I don't know what to do.
- 哦，我不知道该怎么办。
I guess this place belongs
to the gym guys now.
我想这个地方属于
现在去健身房吧。
- Don't leave me, SpongeBob!
- 别离开我，海绵宝宝！
Wait, what am I saying?
等等，我在说什么？
- Help us!
- 帮助我们！
[customers groaning]
- Hungry!
[顾客呻吟]
- 饿了！
- [chomping manically]
- [疯狂地咀嚼]
- What are you all
doing out here?
-你们都是什么人
在这里做什么？
You should just go home.
你应该回家了。
- We can't go home.
- 我们不能回家。
There's no Krabby Patties
at home.
没有蟹肉饼
在家里。
I need my Krabby Patties, man!
我需要我的蟹肉饼，伙计！
[wailing]
You gotta help me!
[哀号]
你得帮帮我！
- Help us!
- Help, help!
- 帮助我们！
- 救命，救命！
- Krabby Patties--that's it!
- 蟹黄饼——就是这样！
Those gym guys have forgotten
the simple, greasy pleasure
那些健身的人都忘记了
简单、油腻的快乐
of munching on a Krabby Patty,
and we need to remind them.
咀嚼蟹黄饼，
我们需要提醒他们。
[bubbling]
[冒泡]
[all grunting forcefully]
[所有人都用力咕哝]
[thud]
- Huh?
[砰]
- 啊？
surfer music]
冲浪者音乐]
[customers grumbling angrily]
[顾客愤怒地抱怨]
- SpongeBob, you're ruining
Larry's pump sesh.
- 海绵宝宝，你毁了
拉里的泵塞什。
- Larry, you're ruining
the Krusty Krab!
- 拉里，你毁了
蟹堡王！
- Get 'em, men!
- 抓住他们，伙计们！
both: [growling]
两人：[咆哮]
- Fire!
- 火！
* *
**
[together]
Mmm!
[一起]
嗯！
- [grunts]
Get over here!
- [咕哝]
过来这里！
- Mmm.
Oh, gimme, gimme!
- 嗯。
哦，给我，给我！
[munching]
[咀嚼]
- Give him a single!
- 给他一张单曲！
Give him a double with cheese!
给他一份双份奶酪！
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[tranquil music]
[安静的音乐]
* *
**
- Yeah!
- 是的！
[jazzy music]
[爵士乐]
all: Huh?
[munching]
全体：啊？
[咀嚼]
- Give into the flavor, Larry!
- 尝尝味道吧，拉里！
[metal clanking]
- Never!
[金属叮当作响]
- 从来没有！
- He's too fast.
We need a distraction.
- 他太快了。
我们需要分散注意力。
[grunts]
Here, use this.
[咕哝]
在这里，用这个。
- [grunts weakly]
- [微弱地咕哝]
- No, you gotta keep
your elbow--
- 不，你必须保留
你的肘部——
[munching]
[咀嚼]
[tranquil music]
- [exhales]
[安静的音乐]
- [呼气]
- [swallows] Oh!
Greasy, fatty,
- [吞咽]哦！
油腻的，肥腻的，
sticky, and gummy!
It's delicious!
又粘又粘！
真好吃！
Larry's been a fool.
拉里是个傻瓜。
I've spent all my time
working on my muscles
我已经用尽我所有的时间
锻炼我的肌肉
when I could've been working
on these delicious sandwiches.
当我可以工作的时候
在这些美味的三明治上。
[sobbing softly]
What's--
[轻声抽泣]
什么是——
what's wrong with me?
我怎么了？
- Now those
are some sad pecs.
- 现在那些
是一些悲伤的胸肌。
- Aw, don't be sad, Larry.
You were just trying
- 哦，别伤心，拉里。
你只是在尝试
to help people get into shape.
帮助人们塑身。
- [blows snot]
- [流鼻涕]
[all chomping]
[全部咀嚼]
[all groaning]
[全都呻吟]
- Eh--looks like your gym
has some new customers.
- 呃--看起来像你的健身房
有一些新客户。
[bubbling]
[冒泡]
- Somebody, let me out
of this thing already!
- 谁来放我出去吧
已经有这件事了！
- [singing]
Home sweet home.
- [唱歌]
温馨的家。
[customers chewing]
Hmm?
[顾客咀嚼]
嗯？
[cheery music]
[欢快的音乐]
* *
**
- Order up!
- 订购吧！
- [chewing]
- [咀嚼]
- [sighs happily]
Everything's just how I left it.
- [高兴地叹气]
一切都还是我离开时的样子。
[light twangy music]
[轻快的鼻音音乐]
* *
**